His name is LeBron James and he plays for LA
It would feel so good and make a big difference
If I could see him play
As I go to my living room
Don't know what imma do
If I hear he ain't gon' play
'Cause I made a bet or two
That he's gonna shoot 10 threes, get 10 reads, and then the Lakers ain't gon' lose
And they got Luka Don, A. Reaves and then LeBron
The real big three
They gave up A. D. because they needed change
And you gots to say his name
His name is LeBron James
I'm talking about the man on the Lakers (LeBron)
I'm asking you to say his name (LeBron James)
And no message could've been any clearer
If you wanna make the world a better place
Take a look at the sky and say his name, yeah
LeBron, LeBron
LeBron is who we love
The best there ever was
It's [email contact@bronify.love if you decipher this]
Now when the king is gone
And he's not in the league
Who do we, what do we go watching on the TV screen
Yeah they got Luka Don, but if there's no LeBron
You won't see me (what don't you see)
Even if they added Cleaveland to Miami Heat
But out of all these other teams
The team that did it for me
I'm talking about the man on the Lakers (LeBron)
I'm asking you to say his name (LeBron James)
And no message could've been any clearer
If you wanna make the world a better place
Take a look at the sky and say his name, yeah
I'm talking about the man on the Lakers (LeBron)
I'm asking you to say his name (LeBron James)
And no message could've been any clearer
If you wanna make the world a better place
Take a look at the sky and say his name, yeah
I'm talking about the man on the Lakers (LeBron)
I'm asking you to say his name (LeBron James)
And no message could've been any clearer
If you wanna make the world a better place
Better look at the sky and say his name
Gotta watch him play while you got the time
'Cause it won't be long until the man retires
Go watch that man, LeBron, that man (LeBron)
The GOAT, that man
You know, that man (LeBron James)
You know, you know, come on, the GOAT